(Bernadette:)This is so exciting. If Leonard
and Penny get back together...
(Bernadette:)...Howard and I can go
on double dates with them.
(Amy:)How come you never invite
Sheldon and me on a double date?
(Bernadette:)Uh...
(Bernadette:)How's it going in there, Penny?
(Penny:)Just a sec.
(Penny:)Too much?
(Sheldon:)- Yes.
- No.
(Penny:)Okay. Just hang on.
(Amy:)You just can't handle her raw sexuality,
can you?
(Bernadette:)When did you and Leonard break up?
(Penny:)Uh, about two years ago.
(Bernadette:)Why do you think
he asked you out again?
(Penny:)I don't know.
- Maybe he's dying.
(Amy:)That would be so romantic.
(Penny:)He's not dying.
(Amy:)Too bad.
If he were, she could throw him in bed
and ride him right up until he flatlines.
(Penny:)How about this?